Thank you for watching!
Thank you for your hard work
Happy New Year, Kotoyoro!
Well, it's decided!
It's a little bit old-fashioned...
I know it's been a while, but...
Mr. Himura, what will you do today?
Let's go!
Nogizaka Mitsuhi Grand New Year's Party!
Yes!
It's been a month since the new year began.
Today, we're going to have a big New Year's party where the teams will face off against each other.
And we're going to have our traditional New Year's party with more entertainment!
And
The winning team will receive a luxurious prize!
Luxurious goods!
This time it's a little more luxurious because everyone's boo-booing!
Wow!
Especially the plums.
He said something like, "Why don't we each get a Shine Muscat?
I'm preparing something nice for you today.
Finally!
Let's play the first game.
Okay, fine.
Mr. Himura, first game, please.
First game is here.
Dragon Boat Ace.
Yes!
A speed race astride a giant dragon in honor of this year's picture and win!
After one lap around the course, which turns back at Nisson, you fall back.
The team that finishes first gets 5 points!
There will be tables, so watch out!
There's also equipment.
It's Kimura, please.
It's Kimura 52, please, this year.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Dragon boat races, get ready!
Start it up!
Spin it, spin it, spin it!
We've got to get them all!
It's got to go all the way in!
I'm trying to get my ass up here!
I need to get my ass up!
Come on!
I gotta back it up!
Come on, come on! Back it up, back it up!
Whoa!
Imai, the Himura team is starting!
The Himura team is starting!
What the hell is the Himura team doing!
Oh, no!
This way! This way!
This way! This way! This way! This way!
Go, go, go!
Go around! Turn!
Turn!
I'm out of here! He's gone!
Turn! Turn!
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no!
Come on!
If you're all in, you win!
All in, you win!
Last one!
Laughter.
Laughter
So, the Nimura team won!
Mr. Himura cheering for the other team, saying, "Go for the Himura team!
Hey, hey, hey!
They're like, "What are you doing?
We're winning, we're winning, we're winning!
And then he calmly said, "We're the Nimura team!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Five points for this!
Yay!
That's good.
But the GoPro here has already been reamed out.
Oh, no, no, no.
Cleave, Cleave, Cleave.
Let's play the next game, Mr. Himura, please.
Let's go!
No English allowed in karaoke.
No English allowed!
The contestants will sing a song from Nogizaka in a relay and compete for karaoke points.
However, if English is spoken during the song, the contestants will translate it into Japanese and sing it on the spot.
At the end of the contest, points are awarded by subtracting the points for mistakes in Japanese translation from the karaoke score.
First, the four members of the Nimura team took on the challenge.
I don't know the lyrics to "Coffee", but if it comes out
I'm not sure if there's a lyric about coffee, but if it comes out, I'll say "black bean water.
That's what you're talking about... coffee!
Now, the Himura team!
First song
"Girls Rule.
It's totally Girl's Rule.
Okay, let's start the music.
This is scary.
We're in the red.
It is.
I've got a lot of time to think about this.
First things first.
Yo.
Let's do it.
big talk
indion
total
U.S.
id
a 친 sensory
From the window made popular by the crowd, white and glistening
the sound of waves approaching
Wrap the bath cloth around you
I'll change into March in 10 seconds
Nothing in there that we can't show each other.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten
In the middle of summer
They fall in love and graduate
Girls rule
I fall in love with you
We cry together all the time
You made me happy
Girl's rule
To father and mother
I'll tell you a secret.
Don't laugh
Fill it up.
On this day
The name in your ear
A ship
Someday
Till I remember this day
Ah, the score
88.424 points.
88 is good, right?
How about that? Try it.
It's pen-pushing.
I'm not confused at all.
You know what I mean.
Let's see how you did in English from here.
Okay.
I feel like rides are too broad.
Like a square vehicle that can still accommodate a lot of people.
You know, like a bus.
Maybe you should be more specific.
Okay, minus one?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, well... I don't blame you.
The members Endo mentioned are his friends.
My friends.
What do you think? Friends?
Club members.
Well, I'm not sure about this, but I'd like to have some company.
Okay, okay, that's great.
What's wrong with this?
A bath towel, right, Mr. Himura?
It's a bath cloth.
No, no, a bath cloth... maybe not a bath towel.
A bath towel.
The cloth you wipe your body with when you get out of the bath.
You have to be that specific, don't you?
But wait a minute.
We'll do this later.
I'll tell you too.
Then we'll give you a minus one.
Okay, now we have a standard.
That one's no good.
Well, the next one's okay.
Well, this is Endo... one, two, three, two, three, two, one... that's all we have.
There's no other way.
That's right.
Girl rules.
Different girls rule.
This isn't perfect anymore.
Yes, it is... the girls' rule.
But you changed it here, didn't you, Mr. Himura?
This is wrong.
It's not a rule.
I made a mistake.
You took the time to tell me this.
No, I can't hear you now.
I'm sorry, I wanted to make a mistake.
You got a minus one here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm dragging you down.
I'll give it a score of 85.424, minus three.
It's good, it's good.
I wonder what song is going to go there.
I don't care if it's in English, as long as it's that good.
If I do that actuary's head, I'll be in trouble.
Next, Shitara's team will try their hand at the following song...
Come on, shampoo!
Here it is! Come on, shampoo!
Don't make me think about it, let's start the song!
Lukewarm, lukewarm.
Shampoo, you don't have to do that.
Start the music!
Oh no!
I'm in!
Yay!
I did the same thing.
Here you go!
Yeah!
I'm thinking so hard.
I wonder what's coming.
Come on, Semphers' die
Semphers die
Semphers die nice
That's good
It's good.
It's so good.
Come on, Semphers' dai
Someday tomorrow night they'll bring me back
I'll be waiting
I made a mistake.
Hang in there
a bag of white short sleeves is also growing
In a tub with no water, you were cleaning the big one, the one you live in the middle of.
I'm a tube of water coming out, squinting at the end of it.
I'll show you a rainbow in the mist...
I was joking around
More than anyone.
I want to feel you closest to me.
I always want to feel you.
Come here, senior.
When you turn around, you move slowly.
I stare at your hair Come here, 1,800 years old
Beside you, the egret, the heron, the egret's song, it reached me, too.
Lastly, you said "hairdressing.
Score: 86.046 yen. Good, good, good.
It's just expensive. It's shampoo. It's shampoo.
Fine play. Perfect.
You got me. It's a hair cleanser.
Nice work bringing that out. You knew it was a hair cleanser.
Shampoo is hair cleanser. It's all settled.
It's all set.
I'm happy for you, too.
The third shirt, the white short-sleeved one, it says "robe.
Clothes. I know what a white short-sleeved robe is.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a lot of shirts after that.
Surprising. What do you say?
The bath cloth was a no-no, right?
That's right. There's the bath part.
I'm talking about the bath towels.
That's no good.
There's only a robe.
No!
Don't say it!
No.
I was a little hard on you earlier.
So this is no good?
No.
No, no, no.
No water.
No water in the pool.
Yes, yes, yes.
Not even close.
No, no, no, no. Why not?
It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK.
Say "OK" and get the pool.
It's hard to think of it all at once, isn't it?
It's the original pool orchestra.
I don't know.
I don't know if the pool originated from an orchestra or not.
I don't know if it's an orchestra or a swimming pool.
It's not an orchestra.
Wait a minute, if you do that, Yumiki's gonna be in the minus column for a long time.
You use a deck brush.
It's got a brush in it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm talking about the brush.
Next, the hose.
The one that comes out with regular water.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You said "regular water hose".
Okay, then.
We're teammates.
There's something going on, Yumiki.
They're teammates.
I don't want to do this.
They'll cut my points.
Shave it off.
Shampoo's here.
Hair cleanser.
Slow motion... slow motion... slow motion... slow motion... slow motion... slow motion.
Perfect, right?
The last shampoo, right?
Hairwash.
It sounds like a hair wash.
All out.
Wait a minute. How many points minus?
Minus four points.
So the score was 82.04.
That's such a point difference.
A point difference like this.
But you know what?
We can get back on track.
You're Yumiki, right?
Daruma-san fell down, testing our bond.
Daruma-san fell down, a test of our bond.
Nijinhaori, throw the mandarin oranges into your mouth
Nijinhaori, put a mandarin orange in your mouth.
Let's play the next game, Mr. Himura, please.
Let's play Nijinhaori and Sanpaku Dharma-san ga Tumbled Relay
While playing "Dharma fell down," the three-legged and two-legged relay teams face off.
First, the tripod team holds the oranges and moves forward in Dharma Sansanta Tumbledown, while the haori team moves forward in Nijinhaori.
The Ninin-haori team stops when the demon turns around, peels off one of the mandarin oranges and puts them all in their mouth.
The team that touches the demon first wins!
The game is a test of the bond between the two teams.
Who will win in this game that tests the bond between two people?
Kuromi and Eokine, how fast can these two get the mandarin oranges in their mouths?
If they don't swallow all of them and they move, we're back to the start. If the oranges move, we're back to the start.
Let's start. Let's go.
Let's get started. Everyone's getting up to speed.
It's early... it's almost there...
Daruma-san fell down.
He's not here yet.
Mr. Daruma fell down.
He hasn't moved. That's good.
Mr. Daruma fell down
He's got room to make a piece of paper.
Daruma-san fell down.
Didn't he just move?
He didn't move.
Please return to the start of the Nimura team.
He did move.
The bird took it.
Don't worry, it'll work.
Careful, careful!
Bodhidharma fell down.
Bodhidharma fell down
It's okay, it's okay.
The team below got the oranges, too.
Ichinose, it looks like your hand.
Your face and hands are in sync.
Daruma-san fell down.
They're starting to turn toward the store.
The three-legged team is ready to go as soon as they finish eating!
Daruma-san fell down.
He's moving right along.
The fastest team, the Himura team, has already come this far!
Daruma-san fell down.
He put half of it in his mouth.
He's in.
Don't move!
It's in!
The white oranges are kind of buzzing.
Next, you two can start the worst scene ever.
Daruma-san fell down.
Wait!
You're just in time.
Mr. Yoda, you're right on the edge.
Careful, careful, careful!
Bodhidharma fell down.
Daruma-san fell down.
Wait a minute, he's trying to eat the oranges with the peel still on the outside!
If you move now, you'll have to start from the beginning.
Here we go!
Daruma fell down.
If you don't eat the oranges, you won't be able to win the game.
Daruma something fell down
Daruma something fell down.
Push, push, touch...
Eat up, eat up!
It's coming!
Here he comes! Here we go!
Daruma touch!
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Yoda's going a little hard. He's going a little hard.
You want to win, don't you?
Here's the goal!
Five points.
That's great!
Iki peeled oranges with a bang, and it only took about three times!
That's right.
Two times, two times.
I took two bites of the "kapa".
We were working well together.
And when I got to this point, I did it with my face and then I did it with my gun.
That's right.
Let's continue with this one.
Mr. Himura, please.
Entertainment corner.
Entertainment.
Here they come.
Shall we wait?
It's a common occurrence at banquets.
It's the entertainment corner, isn't it?
I'll get right to it.
Let's hear it for the first pair.
Here it comes! There it is!
Yes!
No, it's out... the player representative.
It's out! He's out! He's out!
Congratulations!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
I'm Mayu
I'm Shiori
I'm Minami
That's great!
The quality is a little high.
I didn't know who you were the first time you came out.
I just wanted to say hello.
Say hello.
Hello again, everyone!
Out of the box with individuality and freedom
Let's stick out!
We are the new Nogizaka Leaders!
They're amazing!
I can't believe they're dancing.
How long have they been practicing?
On the day of the show.
Today?
We can do it today?
You can do it.
That's what I'm talking about.
Your socks are a little different.
I like it.
They all have their names in blue.
That's awesome!
That was so cool.
Here we go again this year.
The New Year's party heats up with the arrival of that star.
Oh, wow.
Oh, there are three microphones this time.
I wonder if there are three of them.
Let's go.
Alfie.
It's Alfie.
I'm in a café with about 40 people, exactement 40 people.
I've been in about 40 cafes.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for watching.
LOL!
I just said baby kanbak.
Governor General of Shibata Zan? That's what I meant.
Tomisato joined, then Shokichi joined.
Shokichi, right? Not some real musician
Was it Shokichi? There are people like that, aren't there?
I didn't know... seriously... Shokichi looks good... Your hair looks good like that...
Yes, unexpectedly, it suits him. It suits him, it suits him
And Shibata... he can do it as long as Shibata stays
In figures... What's with Shibata?
Are you taking requests? He wants to see it again.
But his beard was renewed.
It's really a wig shop's beard.
They're trying to improve the quality.
It's in a box, and the pins are flying off the beard.
Two years in a row. Oh, that's interesting.
I wish I could see it.
I wish I could see it!
I'm so happy for you.
You have to see the aluminum.
It's not going to start, is it?
The audition for the 6th term starts on February 2nd!
Check out the official site!
Next time, the second half of the show will be even more exciting!
Everyone laughed at the even more upgraded entertainment!
Hello, this is Himikina from Nogizaka46!
What did you eat today?
There is something I want you all to try!
It's omu-rice!
When I eat omelette rice, no matter who I am
It makes me feel nostalgic and warm
I wanted to bring you all to that feeling.
I hope you will all eat omu-rice today!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you for watching!